Guide to the Gerard Salton papers
Salton, Gerard papers
- Series IV. Professional Papers Writings Books
  - Referees (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - H.A. Reich, An Experimental System for Time-Shared On-line Data Acquisition (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - P.A. Reich, Competence, Performance and Relational Networks (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Peter A. Reich, The English Auxiliaries: A Relational Network Description (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - S. Regnier, Problems of Classification (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - E.M. Reingold, Establishing Lower Bounds on Algorithms - a Survey (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Edward M. Reingold, Infix to Prefix Translation: The Insufficiency of a Pushdown Stack (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Edward M. Reingold, A Nonrecursive List Moving Algorithm (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - E.M. Reingold and A. Ian Stocks, Simple Proofs of Lower Bounds for Polynomial Evaluation (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Edward M. Reingold, On the Optimality of Some Set Algorithms (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - J. Francis Reintjes, Hardware (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - J. Francis Reintjes, Interlibrary Loan Through Election (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - P. Reisner, Human Factors in Query Language (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Reitan (Buffalo) (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Walter Reitman, Autonote: A Personal Information Storage and Retrieval System (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - A. Reiter, On-line Information Retrieval on a Small Computer (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - R. Reiter, A Study of a Model of Parallel Computation (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Raymond Reiter, Initiation Timing in a Model for Parallel Computation (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - C.J. Date and Alain Pirotte, Relational Languages (Model) (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - Relational View of Document Databases (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - Relevance Measure (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - Residue Arithmetic (Box 53, Folder 63)
  - A. Resnick, Relative Effectiveness of Document Titles and Abstracts for Determining Relevance of Documents (Box 53, Folder 64)
  - A. Resnick and C.B. Hensley, The Use of Diary and Interview Techniques in Evaluating a System for Disseminating Technical Information (Box 53, Folder 65)
  - Mitchel Resnick and Fred Martin, Children and Artificial Life (Box 53, Folder 66)
  - H.L. Resnikoff, A Theory of the Turn-Around Time Distribution for Batch Processing (Box 53, Folder 67)
  - H.L. Resnikoff and J.L. Dolby, Access: A Study of Information Storage and Retrieval with Emphasis on Library Information Systems (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 68)
  - H.L. Resnikoff and J.L. Dolby, Access: A Study of Information Storage and Retrieval with Emphasis on Library Information Systems (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 69)
  - H.L. Resnikoff and J.L. Dolby, Access: A Study of Information Storage and Retrieval with Emphasis on Library Information Systems (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 70)
  - Notes/Addendum to ACCESS (Resnikoff) (Box 53, Folder 71)
  - H. Resnikoff, Computer Projections (Box 53, Folder 72)
  - H.L. Resnikoff, On the Problems of Information Science (Box 53, Folder 73)
  - Howard L. Resnikoff, On Information Systems with Emphasis on the Mathematical Sciences (Box 53, Folder 74)
  - Resnikoff Book List (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 75)
  - Resnikoff Book List (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 76)
  - Resnikoff Book List (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 53, Folder 77)
  - Resnikoff List (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 78)
  - Resnikoff List (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 79)
  - Responsa Project (Box 53, Folder 80)
  - Retirement (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Retrieval Technologies, Inc. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - John W. Rettenmeyer, File Ordering and Retrieval Costs (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - R. Rettig, Science and Public Policy (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - John C. Reynolds, Cogent Programming Manual (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - James F. Rial, Metric Searching as an Extension of Coordinate Indexing (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - J.F. Rial, Rout Document Retrieval Evaluation (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Phyllis Richmond, Contribution Toward a New Generalized Theory of Classification (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Phyllis A. Richmond, Transformation and Organization of Information Content... (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - D.T. Richnell, First Thoughts on Dainton (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - J.T. Rickman, Boolean Relevance Feedback (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - C. Rieger, Language Comprehension (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Burghard Rieger, Fuzzy Structural Semantics on a Generative Model of Vague Natural Language Meaning (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Burghard Rieger, Unscharfe Semantik Naturlicher Spracher - Fuzzy Semantics (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - C.K. Riesbeck and R.C. Schank, Comprehension by Computer (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Malcolm Rigby, Standardization for Classification in Computerized Documentation Systems (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - E.M. Riseman, Contextual Word Recognition Using Binary Diagrams (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Ronald L. Rivest, Analysis of Associative Retrieval Algorithms (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - R.L. Rivest et al, Crypto Systems (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Ron Rivest, A Fast, Stable, Minimum-Storage Sorting Algorithm (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - R.L. Rivest, Game Tree Searching by Min/Max Aproximation (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - R.L. Rivest, Optimal Arrangement of Keys (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Herbert Roback, Congress and the Science Budget (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - A. Hood Roberts, Selected Bibliography in Programmed Instruction (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Martin B. Roberts, A Generalized Recognizer for Finite State Languages (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - M. de V. Roberts, Associative Memories and the One-Level Store (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - E.E. Robertson, The Parametric Description of Retrieval Tests (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - S.E. Robertson, The Probabilistic Character of Relevance (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - S.E. Robertson/Maron/Cooper, Two Competing Models (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - S.E. Robertson and D. Teather, A Statistical Analyisis of Retrieval Tests: A Bayesian Approach (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - S.E. Robertson, On the Nature of Fuzz (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Stephen E. Roberston, Explicit and Implicit Variables in Information (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - S.E. Robertson, Theories and Models in Information Retrieval (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - S.E. Robertson, Relevance Weight Estimation (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - S.E. Robertson, Term Frequency and Term Value (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - S.E. Robertson and K. Sparck Jones, Relevance Weighting of Search Terms (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Robertson, Van Rijsbergen and Porter, Probabilistic Models of Indexing and Searching (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - A.E. Robertson, Natural Language Communication (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Jane J. Robinson, Automatic Parsing and Fact Retrieval (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Jane J. Robinson, Methods for Obtaining Corresponding Phrase Structure and Dependency Grammer (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - Jane J. Robinson, Preliminary Codes and Rules for Automatic Parsing of English (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Jane J. Robinson, The Transformation of Sentences for Information Retrieval (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Harold Robinson, Computer-Detectable Semantic Strcutures (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - J.J. Rocchio, Assignment with Property Constraints (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Miriam Rodin and Burton Rodin, Student Evaluations of Teachers (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Robotics (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - Frank B. Rogers, Costs of Operating an Information Retrieval Service (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - P. Rohatgi, Generalized Models for IR (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - Loll N. Rolling, Compilation of Thesauri for Use in Computer Systems (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - L. Rolling, Euratom Thesaurus, Part III, Terminology Charts used Euratom's Nuclear Documentation System (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - L. Rolling, Graphic Display of Concepts (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - Loll N. Rolling, International Networks: The European Situation (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - L. Rolling, Indexing Consistency, Quality and Efficiency (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - L. Rolling, Un Repertoire de Mots-Cles Pour La Documentation Mecanisee (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - Sydney C. Rome and Beatrice K. Rome, Automated Learning Process (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - Rome Air Development Center (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - Rome Air Development Center (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 54, Folder 57)
  - Rome Air Development Center (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 54, Folder 58)
  - G.F. Romerio and L. Cavara, Assessment Studies of Documentation Systems (Box 54, Folder 59)
  - G.F. Romerio, Performance of the SDS/RECON European Network (Box 54, Folder 60)
  - P. Rooets, South African Information Retrieval (Box 54, Folder 61)
  - D. Roots, Use of CTSS in a Teaching Environment (Box 54, Folder 62)
  - C.C.J. Roothaan, The Man Machine Project (Box 54, Folder 63)
  - M.E. Rorvig, Psychometrics and Information Retrieval (Box 54, Folder 64)
  - Milton E. Rose, Computer Costs: Two Alternatives (Box 54, Folder 65)
  - Saul Rosen, Electronix Computers: A Historical Survey (Box 54, Folder 66)
  - R.C. Rosenberg, D.W. Kennedy and R.A. Humphrey, A Low-Cost Output Terminal for Time-Shared Computers (Box 54, Folder 67)
  - Victor Rosenberg, A Study of Statistical Measures and for Predicting Terms Used to Index Documents (Box 54, Folder 68)
  - Frank Roseblatt, Intelligent-Automaton Perceptron (Box 54, Folder 69)
  - Pierre Rosenstiehl, L'Arbre Minimum d'un Graphe (Box 54, Folder 70)
  - Robert F. Rosin, An Organization of an Associative Cryogenic Computer (Box 54, Folder 71)
  - J.P. Roth (Symposium Paper), Combinatorial Topological Methods in the Synthesis of Switch Circuits (Box 54, Folder 72)
  - Paul J. Roth and E.G. Wagner, Algebraic Topological Methods for the Synthesis of Switching Systems, Part III (Box 54, Folder 73)
  - D.H. Rothenberg, An Efficiency Model and a Performance Function for an Information Retrieval System (Box 54, Folder 74)
  - J. Rothman, N.Y. Times (Box 54, Folder 75)
  - R. Rousseau et. al., Similarity Measures (Box 54, Folder 76)
  - R. Rousseau, Extended Boolean Retrieval (Box 54, Folder 77)
  - Bernard Roy, De La Theorie Des Graphes et de Ses Applications en Recherche Operationelle (Box 54, Folder 78)
  - M. Rubinoff, S. Bergman, H. Cantin, R. Rapp, Easy English, A Language for Information Retrieval Through a Remote Typewriter Console (Box 54, Folder 79)
  - M. Rubinoff, W. Franks, D.C. Stone, Description of an Experiment Investigating Term Relationships as Interpreted by Humans (Box 54, Folder 80)
  - Mary James Ruhl, Chemical Documents and Their Titles: Human Concept Indexing vs. KWIC-Machine Indexing (Box 54, Folder 81)
  - David E. Rumelhart, Parallel Distributed Processing: Explorations in the Microstructure of Cognition (Box 54, Folder 82)
  - Stuart Russel, On Provably RALPHS, and, Principles of Metareasoning (Box 54, Folder 83)
  - Francis John Russo, A Heuristic Approach to Alternative Routing in a Job Shop (Box 54, Folder 84)
  - J.D. Rutledge, On Ianov's Program Schemata (Box 54, Folder 85)
  - Peter Turner Rux, Design and Evaluation of a Glass Delay Line Content-Addressable Memory System (Box 54, Folder 86)
  - Adrian Ruyle, The Status of Systems for On-Line Mathematical Assistance (Box 54, Folder 87)
  - V.I. Ruzhanskiy (JPRS 30323), Algorithms for Pattern Recognition (Box 54, Folder 88)
  - Vincent J. Ryan and V.A. Dearing, Computerized Text Editing and Processing with Built-In Indexing (Box 54, Folder 89)
  - Thomas L. Saaty, Operations Research: Some Contributions to Mathematics (Box 54, Folder 90)
  - G.M. Sacco, OTTER: An Information Retrieval System for Office Automation (Box 54, Folder 91)
  - W.M. Sachs, Associative Retrieval Through the Theory of Fuzzy Sets (Box 54, Folder 92)
  - R. Sacks-Davis, Multi-Key Access (Box 54, Folder 93)
  - R. Sacks-Davis and R. Wilkinson, Syntax in Retrieval (Box 54, Folder 94)
  - R. Sacks-Davis and K. Chattrasophon, A Ranking Algorithm (Box 54, Folder 95)
  - H. Sackman, W. Erickson and E. Grant, Exploratory Experimental Studies Comparing Online and Offline Programming Performance (Box 54, Folder 96)
  - C.R. Sage, R.R. Anderson and D. Fitzwater, Adaptive Information Dissemination (Box 54, Folder 97)
  - Naomi Sager, Computational Linguistics: Steps Towards Application (Box 54, Folder 98)
  - Naomi Sager, A Computer String-Grammar of English, Parts I-III (Box 54, Folder 99)
  - N. Sager, IFIP Congress 1962, Syntactic Analysis (Box 54, Folder 100)
  - N. Sager and L. Hirschman, Information Structure in Language (Box 54, Folder 101)
  - N. Sager and R. Grishman, The Restriction Language for Computer Grammars of Natural Language (Box 54, Folder 102)
  - N. Sager, Syntactic Formatting of Science Information (Box 54, Folder 103)
  - Sagiv, Y., C. Delobel, et. al. - Equivalence & Dependencies of Logic (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Salisbury, B.A. Jr. and E.H. Stiles - The Use of the B-Coefficient in Information Retrieval (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Salkoff, M. - Preliminary Report on the Application of the String Program to Information Retrieval of Physics Texts (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Saltzer, J.H. - "CTSS Technical Notes" - MAC-TR-16 - Project MAC Abstract (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Saltzer, Jerome Howard - Traffic Control in a Multiplexed Computer System (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Sammet, J.E. - "A Method of Combining ALGOL and COBOL" (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Sammet, Jean E. - An Annotated Descriptor Based Bibliography on the Use of Computers for Non-Numerical Mathematics (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Sammet, Jean and Robert Kenney - Description of Time-Shared FORMAC (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Sammet, Jean E. - Survey of Formula Manipulation (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Sammon, John W. Jr. - Interactive Pattern Analysis and Classification, July 1970 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Samuel, A.L. - Some Studies in Machine Learning Using the Game of Checkers II - Recent Progress (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Samuel, Arthur L. - "Time-Sharing on a Multiconsole Computer" - MAC-TR-17 - Thom. J. Watson Res. Center, March 1965 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Samuel, N.M., et. al. - Methodology and Results of an Industrial Part Survey (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Samuelson, Kjell - Free-TEXT INDEXing to Meet COMPUTers Halfway (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Sandek, L. - Information Retrieval (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Saracevic, Tefko - Comparative Effects of Titles, Abstracts and Full Texts on Relevance Judgments (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Saracevic, T. - The Effects of Question, Analysis and Searching Strategy on Performance of Retrieval Systems: Selected Results from an Experimental Study (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Saracevic, Tefko, Manager - An Inquiry Into Testing of Information Retrieval Systems, Pt. 1 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Saracevic, Tefko, Manager - An Inquiry Into Testing of Information Retrieval Systems, Pt. 2 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Saracevic, Tefko, Manager - An Inquiry Into Testing of Information Retrieval Systems, Pt. 3 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Saracevic, T. - Relevance is Bradforsion (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Saracevic, Tefko - Linking Research and Teaching (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Saracevic, T. - Selected Results from an Inquiry Into Testing of Information Retrieval Systems (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Saracevic, T. - Ten Years of Relevance Experimentation - A Summary and Synthesis of Conclusions (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Saracevic, T. - Relevance - A Review & Framework (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Saracevic, Tefko - Towards the Identification & Control of Variables in Information Retrieval Experimentation (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Saracevic, T. - STI in Less Developed Countries (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - LEGO Design (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Sastri, Madagula I. - A Linguistic Approach to Relevance Judgement (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - SATCOM: Report on the Initial Conference of SATCOM Consulting Correspondents (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Satterthwait, Arnold C. - Sentence-for-Sentence Translation: An Example (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Sattler, P. - Vector Correction Measure (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Savage, T.R. - SDI Bibliography - 1 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Savage, T.R. - The Interpretation of SDI Data (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Savage, T.R. - "The Preparation of Auto-Abstracts on the IBM 704 Data Processing System" (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Schank, Roger, N.M. Goldman and Charles Rieger - Inference and Paraphrase by Computer (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Schank, R.C. - Gettysburg Address (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Schank, R.C. - Inference in Conceptual Dependency (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Schank, R.C. - Fourteen Primitive Actions (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Schank, Roger - The Role of Memory in Language (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Schank, Roger - Causality and Reasoning (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Schank, R.C. - Interestingness-Inference (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Schank, R.C. - Noun Groups Analysis (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Schank, R.C. - "Semantics in Conceptual Analysis" (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Schank, R.C. - Conceptual Dependency (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Schank, Roger C., Larry Tesler, and Sylvia Weber - Conceptual Case-Based Natural Language Analysis (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Schank, Roger C. - Understanding Paragraphs (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Scharfenberg, K.F., P.H. Smith, and R.D. Villani - A Concordance Generator (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Schatzoff, M., R. Tsao, and R. Wiig - An Experimental Comparison of Time-Sharing and Batch-Processing (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Schäuble, P. - Improving Retrieval Effectiveness (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Schäuble, P. - Information Retrieval (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Schäuble, P. - (Preference Relations) Compatibility of Retrieval Function (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Schäuble, P., H.P. Frei, and M. Wyle - Assessment of IR Systems (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Schäuble, P. - 1 Year [Correspondence] (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Schäuble, P. (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Schäuble, P. - Multimedia Project (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Schäuble, P. and D. Knaus - Spiper System (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - Scheffer, Emilie - "Recueil De Stemmas (Tome I)" (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - Schek, H.J. - Nested Transactions in Combined DBMS-IRS (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - Schek, H.J. - Reference Stray (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - Schek, H.J. - Text Field Indexing (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Schek, H.J. - On Index Intervals (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Scherr, Allan Lee - An Analysis of Time-Shared Computer Systems (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Scheuch, Erwin - "Research Proposal to Nat. Sci. Foundation" (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - Schiebler, W.D. and G.W. Thomas - An Algorithm for Compaction of Alphanumeric Data (Box 55, Folder 65)
  - Schiller, William L., et. al. - A Microprogrammed Intelligent Graphics Terminal (Box 55, Folder 66)
  - Schiminovich, Samuel - Automatic Classification and Retr. of Docs. by Means of a Bibliographic Pattern Discovery Algorithm (Box 55, Folder 67)
  - Schlaeppi, M.P. - "A Formal Language for Describing Machine Logic Timing...(LOTIS)" (Box 55, Folder 68)
  - Schlesinger, I.M. - The Influence of Sentence Structure on the Reading Process (Box 55, Folder 69)
  - Schlesinger, S. and L. Shashkin - POSE: A Language for Posing Problems to a Computer (Box 55, Folder 70)
  - Schmid, H.A. and J.R. Swenson - On the Sentence of the Relational Data Model (Box 55, Folder 71)
  - Schmid, H.A. and P.A. Bernstein - Multi-Level Architecture for Relations (Box 55, Folder 72)
  - Schminda, Janusz - Semantischer Code (Box 55, Folder 73)
  - Schneider, John H. - Selective Dissemination and Indexing of Scientific Information (Box 55, Folder 74)
  - Schneider, Klaus - "Fünf Jahre KWIC-Indexing Nach H.P. Luhn" (Box 55, Folder 75)
  - Schneider, M.I. - "State Assignment Algorithm for Clocked Sequential Machines" (Box 55, Folder 76)
  - Schnelle, H. - "CC-AUTOMATA and CF-GRAMMARS" Colloquium Algebraic Ling. and Auto. Theory, Jerusalem, August 24-25, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 77)
  - Schnelle, H. - Automatic Translation (Box 55, Folder 78)
  - Scholl, M. - Dynamic Hash-Coding (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Schuegraf, E.J. and H.S. Heaps - Equifrequent Word Fragments (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Schott, Gerda - Automatische Analyse der Flexionsmorpheme Deutscher Substantive Teilalgorithmus Zum Automatischen Indexieren (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Schroeder, M.R. - Images from Computers and Microfilm Plotters (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Schroeder, M.D. - Performance of Firefly RPC (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Schuegraf, E.J. and R.M. Lea - Associative File Store (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Schuette, W. - Tensor Analysis (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Schultz, Andrew - College of Engineering Annual Report to the President, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Schultz, C.K. - A Generalized Computer Method for Index Production (Section 2) (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Schultz, Claire K. - "A Generalized Computer Method for Informatioin Retrieval" (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Schultz, Claire K. - "Indexing Performance Measured by Comparison of Responses: The Author as Indexer", October 12, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Schutzenberger, M.D. - "On Context-Free Languages and Push-Down Automata" (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Schwarcz, R., J.F. Burger, and R.F. Simmons - A Deductive Question-Answer for Natural Language Inference (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Schwarcz, Robert M. - Linguistic Relativity and the Language Learning Process (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Schwartz, Jules I. - "Command Research Laboratory: Intro to the Time-Sharing System" (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Schwartz, Jules I. - Online Programming (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Schwarz, C. - Auto Syntatic Analysis (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Schwarz, C. - Text Research with Multiword Concepts (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Schwarz, H.R. - "An Introduction to ALGOL 60" (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Schwarz, Harry - Encyclopedic Storage of Scientific and Technical Knowledge (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Scions, H.I. - Placing Trees in Lexicographic Order (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Scorpio - Library of Congress (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Search Express (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Searle, S.R. - CUSTAT, The Cornell University Computer Programs in Statistics (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Searle, J. - Mind-Body Problem (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Sechser, O. - Link Indicators (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Secrest, B.W. - "The IBM 101 Electronic Statistical Machine Applied to Word Analysis of the Dead Sea Scrolls" (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Security (Disks) (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Sedelow, Sally Yeates and Walter A. Sedelow - "A Preface to Computational Stylistics" (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Sedelow, Sally Yeates - Stylistic Analysis Report on the First Year of Research (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Sedelow, Sally Yeates, Walter A. Sedelow Jr., and T. Ruggles - "Some Parameters for Computational Stylistics: Computer Aids to the Use of Traditional Categories in Stylistic Analysis" (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Sedlacek, K. and A. Sychra - The Method of Psychoacoustic Transformation App. to Investigation of Expression in Speech and Music (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - See, Richard - "Machine-Aided Translation and Information Retrieval" (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Segre, Alberto - Dept. of Computer Science (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Seigle, David - Some Aids in the Handling of Missing Data (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Selwyn, Lee L. - The Information Utility (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Semon, W.L. - Bibliography on Switching Theory (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Semon, W. - Synthesis of Series Parallel Network Switching Functions, Monograph 3110 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Senzig, D.N. - "Suggested Timing Notation for the Iverson Notation" (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Settel, B. and P.A. Cochrane - Augmenting Subject Descriptions (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Serrell, R., M.M. Astrahan, G.W. Patterson, and I.B. Pyne - The Evolution of Computing Machines and Systems (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Severance, D.G. - Data Compression (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Severance, D. - Identifier Search Mechanisms: A Study and Generalized Model (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Shalla, Leon - Automatic Analysis of Electronic Digital Circuits Using List Processing (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Shannon, C.E. - "Communication Theory of Secrecy Systems" (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Shannon, C.E. - Prediction and Entropy of Printed English (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Shannon, C.E. - A Symbolic Analysis of Relay and Switching Circuits, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Shannon, Stan and Claudia Henschke - Stat-Pack: A Biostatistical Programming Package (Box 56, Folder 48)